[theme music playing]
Don't you think it's about time
you reinstated me?
I will not reinstate you.
Arnaldo will run for governor
of Poblacion Ardiente
in the next election.
[Jepoy] You got everything
you wanted from me.
I'm of no more use now. Let me go!
[Julio] Bring me Alvarez's head,
and I'll set you free.
There's going to be a new king.
And I'm pretty sure
he will have his own queen.
I will not be pushed
to the sidelines, Auntie.
Especially once I prove to my family
that Ivy Aguas is connected
to Camia Cruz and Madrigal.
And when that happens,
I'll be the hero of the family.
[Diego] They're all cunning.
They might let Jepoy live
as long as he's useful to them.
-And if he isn't?
-They'll kill him.
I need to save Jepoy.
-Get out of my way.
-No.
-What's wrong with you?
-Yes, he's your friend! But I love you!
Ivy, trust me. I'll get Jepoy back.
I'll bring him back safe and sound.
[goon] Madrigal escaped.
Damn it!
[Jepoy] I'm the time bomb
they're waiting on to explode
so they'll find out who you really are.
The danger of them finding out
about your real plans will still be there.
I have to cut ties with you.
[Ivy] I can't believe it.
How did Madrigal manage to escape?
Maybe because he had
an accomplice within our circle?
Don't be stupid.
Or have you forgotten
Miss Aguas' transgressions
against our family?
If you focus on this
unfounded suspicion against Ivy,
we're going to have a problem.
[Emilia] I won't allow my son
to be used by someone
who could betray our family.
That's why I helped you
find Governor Alvarez.
To prove my loyalty to your family.
As for me and Arnaldo, we aren't official.
But once that happens, I'll text you.
When Emilia got sick,
William Alvarez was
the first person I thought of
who could replace her as governor.
He was the perfect choice
for governor on paper.
He was well-educated,
and he came from a good family.
That's why it hurts to admit
and to tell everyone
the truth that the person
I chose to become governor
hid behind a mask.
And behind that mask
was the face of a traitor.
A traitor who found his way
into public office.
The rumors that
you've been hearing are true.
It's true that Governor Alvarez
stole public funds,
which were supposed to be
used for government projects.
Now that he's gone,
may his death be a warning
to all those who are planning
to betray the public's trust.
And, it's only fitting
that the one who'll replace him
is someone who's honest, fearless,
and willing to offer their life
for the future of the residents
of Poblacion Ardiente.
Allow me to introduce to you…
the person who will be
running for governor
in the next election.
He's none other than my grandson,
and the current mayor of this town,
Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo!
[applause]
[Arnaldo] Thank you.
[farmer 1] We will fight for Diego!
Fight!
[Dolfo] We will fight for the
farmers of Poblacion Ardiente!
Fight!
[farmer 2] Long live Diego!
Go, Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
[Arnaldo] My fellowmen,
as your long-term mayor,
I'm asking all of you to
support and join our family
in condemning a corrupt traitor,
William Alvarez.
Along with hunting down
another traitor named Madrigal
and the man who helped him evade justice.
Let's put an end to the silence
they've imposed upon us,
especially when we try to speak
against the current government's actions.
Let's put an end to
the suffering of our fellowmen
under the vicious and unfair
governance of the Ardientes!
Our town won't prosper if we don't get rid
of the weeds that pollute where we live.
[Diego] Let's show the Ardientes
that we're sick and tired
of a political dynasty!
We're sick and tired of crimes
and the oppression of human rights!
Now's the time to establish
a new government.
A government that will truly understand
the problems of its people.
It's time for a new Ardiente!
As your next governor,
I promise you that we will take this town
to even greater heights.
[applause]
-[farmer] Long live Diego!
-[all] Long live Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Ivy, can we talk?
Why? Do you have another issue?
Are you going to call me a leech,
traitor, and manipulator again?
You know, Ivy, those aren't
the only names I can call you.
There are many more.
But that can change, just as
long as you cooperate with me.
[sighs] Get to the point,
Emilia. Cut to the chase.
Okay. I want you to support
my bid for governor.
I need financial backing.
[chuckles]
Emilia, you're making it
a habit to beg money from me.
Why would I lend you money?
You know my loyalty lies
with your son, Arnaldo.
Oh, really?
What you're saying contradicts
what these pictures show.
Let me see.
These? What are you implying?
That I'm Madrigal's accomplice?
Then, why are you so interested
in what could happen to Madrigal?
You even gave us information
so we could pin down Alvarez.
Emilia, you're making me laugh.
You're hilarious.
Just because you can't get what you want
doesn't mean you need
to resort to blackmail.
You're pathetic.
And you are a lying witch.
Emilia. Those pictures are
taken from public events.
They can't prove that
I'm on Madrigal's side,
or that I'm his accomplice.
So, if I were you, fire your investigator
because you're making a fool of yourself.
I know, Emilia, things are not
going well for you.
But please, please, Emilia.
Stop humiliating yourself.
Please.
Mom, I heard that you fought
with Ivy again.
I found something.
Madrigal and Ivy Aguas
are working together.
Oh, come on. This doesn't prove anything!
If that were true,
Ivy would've rescued
Madrigal a long time ago!
Arnaldo, what did that woman
feed you for you
to think that way?
Don't you see?
Can't you see that Ivy is working
with the people betraying us?
And the only reason why we're keeping her
is because of her money!
That's it. Enough.
Arnaldo, I just don't
want you to get hurt.
But you will when you find out
that Ivy is using you.
I said enough.
Okay?
You're just upset because
you didn't become governor,
and Ivy didn't back you up!
And, now?!
You just want everyone
to be miserable just like you!
And how dare you talk to me
that way, Arnaldo?!
How dare you?
This is for you.
It's not too much, but I hope it can help.
[man 1] Thank you, Mayor.
-[man 2] Thank you, Mayor.
-[Arnaldo] Okay.
[Arnaldo] Take care.
I see that you even give money
to the volunteers.
Of course, Miss Aguas.
Money makes the world go round.
Oh, and speaking of money.
I presume you'll also help us financially
with Arnaldo's campaign?
I remember you promised me
something like that.
[chuckles]
Of course, Congressman.
I have faith in Arnaldo.
That's why I'll provide him
one hundred percent
financial support
in his political campaign.
One hundred percent?
So, does that mean you won't
support any other candidate?
Just Arnaldo?
You can count on me, Congressman.
Thank you.
[Camia] What about the noodles?
[farmer 1] We still have plenty
of it, ma'am.
[Camia] All right, you should
eat too, okay?
[Camia] Right. How's it going?
-[farmer 2] It's good, ma'am.
-[Camia] Good.
[farmer 2] I'm about to finish this.
Diego! Nimfa said that her workmates
from San Bartolome
would come and help us too.
-Great!
-They're glad to know
you're running.
They'll support you with your campaign.
They're willing to volunteer.
-Nice.
-Wow.
-Thank you, Nanny.
-I'll tell them that.
Everyone!
Thank you for all your support.
I must admit,
I still don't know how to start,
and I don't have the means
compared to what the Ardientes do.
But every time I see how united we are,
I get the courage to fight.
You can count on us, Diego!
We've always wanted you to run,
but we understand that you didn't want
to go up against your family.
-But you finally woke up.
-Right.
[laughs]
Like all of you, and the people
of Ardiente,
I finally decided to do the right thing.
-[Pandoy] Correct.
-[farmer 3] Right.
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone ringing]
[Fernan] Look, it's almost--
-I'll just take this.
-[Fernan] That's good.
-[Loring] Okay.
-[phone ringing]
Hello, Ivy?
Diego. The Ardientes have
started mobilizing their units.
They're also looking for Jepoy.
Tomorrow, they'll go to the cooperative.
So, be ready.
I just want to tell you
that I may be far away from you,
but you have my full support.
I know, Ivy.
We'll be ready.
There's no turning back, Ivy.
-You should eat first.
-It's good.
[Camia] Take a break.
Everyone!
I've got news.
I received a lead saying
the Ardientes will come here tomorrow.
What? But why?
I know we have yet to come up
with concrete plans…
But we're talking to possible
sponsors and supporters
who could help with Diego's campaign.
Diego, why don't you seek help
from Miss Ivy?
-That's right! Yes!
-Isn't that right, friends?
I mean, she helped us when
the Ardientes took our land before.
So, I'm sure Miss Ivy
will also help Diego.
-[Fernan] Right.
-[Pandoy] She'll help you, son.
Even if she doesn't help financially, her
moral support will be more than enough.
You two are good friends, right?
[Pandoy] That's right.
I'm sorry…
but Miss Aguas decided
to support the Ardientes.
So, it's better for us to do
this without her help this time.
Everyone, let's just eat for now.
-[farmer 4] Come on.
-[Fernan] Talk to him.
-[Pandoy] But…
-All right, Miss Camia.
-[Pandoy] How come? How?
You know what to do.
If you need to search every nook
and cranny in this town, do it.
Until you find Madrigal. Understood?
-Yes, Mayor.
-You can go now.
[Jepoy] Ivy, I'm the key.
I'm the time bomb
they're waiting on to explode
so they'll find out who you really are.
I have to cut ties with you.
I have to stay away from you, Ivy.
I'll leave. But once I come back…
I'll have what I need to bring
the Ardientes to their knees.
Congressman, we checked every
house in Poblacion Ardiente.
No sign of Madrigal.
He probably left town.
Okay, Mario. You may go.
Our enemies should never escape
the claws of the Ardientes.
Grandpa, we cannot waste all our resources
just trying to find Madrigal.
And what do you propose we do?
Ignore the fact that your
traitor of a bodyguard got away?
Okay, I understand.
But you said it yourself.
He's nothing but an insect
that we'll crush
the minute he decides to come back.
For now, we have better things to do.
This is a bitter pill to swallow, Arnaldo.
[Julio sighs]
But, unfortunately, you're right.
Emilia…
Hi, Aunt Claire.
Care for some wine and a whining session?
What are you whining about,
my dear Emilia?
What would you do if your son,
whom you love,
suddenly treats you
like garbage for some woman…
Ivy Aguas?
What else can you do, Emilia?
You can't sabotage
Ivy and Arnaldo every chance you get.
What are you trying to say, Auntie?
Arnaldo may be your son,
but he is his own person.
You can't decide whom he should love.
The only thing you can do is support him,
love him, whatever happens.
Here's your bag, Ivy.
Thanks, Nanny.
I'm just waiting for Arnaldo
then we'll go to the co-op.
Ivy, isn't it hard for you
that you're with Arnaldo
even though you're
actually supporting Diego?
I need to do this.
If I don't, our plans will be ruined.
I also need to go
because my mother's there.
I need to look out for her
and protect her.
-Okay. Just be careful.
-[phone ringing]
-Diego.
-Ivy.
I'll go there as soon
as Arnaldo gets here. Be ready.
We will.
Be careful, Ivy.
-Of course?
-[Carlotta] Mr. Mayor!
Mr. Mayor, you're here.
Mr. Mayor is here, Ivy.
Mr. Mayor, you're a bit early.
Of course.
I'm excited for the grassroots campaign.
Who were you talking to?
A partner. Business in Manila.
I'm sure today's going to be
fruitful and enlightening.
Let's go?
Mr. Mayor.
Diego? Nimfa's co-workers
will be coming all the way
from the other town.
But they're all ready to support you.
[applause]
-Thank you, Mrs. Camia.
-You're welcome, Diego.
-Uncle Pandoy.
-Son.
-[Loring] That's right.
-[Pandoy] Thank you, thank you.
The Ardientes.
Good morning to you all.
Dear friends, how are you all?
We're here to give you
some gifts. Please accept them.
And what's wrong with you people?
Why won't you accept our gifts?
Why? Are you satisfied with
what Camia Cruz is giving you?
And what does this woman
have that we don't?
Show some decency.
You just can't accept that
the people of Ardiente
are rejecting your family's bribes!
Who says those are bribes?
They aren't bribes.
They aren't? Why?
You're only giving us gifts
so you can force us…
-to vote for Mayor Arnaldo!
-You're testing my patience!
We came here out of humility.
Because I know that
we disagree on a lot of things
here in the cooperative.
And then I arrive here,
and I find this Camia woman leading you!
What am I supposed to think?
She's poisoned your minds
and those of our neighbors!
[Emilia] Precisely.
After all of the help
the Ardientes have given you,
this is how you repay us?
What are you all so proud of, anyway?
Who do you think is capable
of leading this town?
Aside from us, the Ardientes?
Who else? Tell us! Who?!
[tense music swelling]
Me.
I will run for governor
against you, Arnaldo.
-Diego for the people!
Viva Ardiente! Viva Ardiente!
-Viva Ardiente!
[farmers] Diego for the people!
[Ardientes' supporters] Viva Ardiente!
[Julio laughing] You?!
Now you're a comedian too.
Who did you take after? Your mother? Hmm?
Well, then.
Let me ask you this, my fellowmen.
Will you really allow
this worthless bastard
to become the governor of this town?
No! Mayor Arnaldo!
[overlapping dialogue]
A good leader isn't measured by his roots…
but by his character.
You should never trust a leader
who's a murderer.
Yes! Arnaldo had all of
Camia Cruz's witnesses killed.
-We'll fight for Diego!
-Viva Ardiente!
[farmers] We'll fight for Diego!
[Ardientes' supporters] Viva Ardiente!
-We'll fight for Diego!
-Viva Ardiente! Viva Ardiente!
[overlapping dialogue]
[Loring] We'll fight for Diego!
Arnaldo, relax. Not here.
There are a lot of people. Relax.
Miss Aguas, why are you
trying to stop Arnaldo?
He's only giving
what this bastard deserves.
Because this worthless man is a traitor!
What now? Cat got your tongue?
That's the truth.
You betrayed our family
with what you're doing.
Think about it, Diego.
How dare you compete with your brother?!
Your own flesh and blood!
I wouldn't be surprised…
if it was you who helped Madrigal escape.
[Julio] You know Madrigal, right?
The same Madrigal who killed Governor…
-Alvarez!
-Liar!
It was you who had Alvarez killed!
You're all murderers!
You're lower than the dirt on this farm!
-That's enough!
-Arnaldo!
-Diego!
-Viva Ardiente!
Stop! That's enough! Stop them!
[clamoring]
[overlapping dialogue]
Viva, Ardiente! Viva, Ardiente!
Viva, Ardiente!
[clamoring]
Diego!
We'll fight for Diego!
-We'll fight for Diego!
-Viva Ardiente!
We'll fight for Diego!
Viva, Ardiente!
[overlapping dialogue]
[clamor continues]
Let's go!
[clamoring]
[indistinct shouting]
[laughing]
What a joke.
You know what?
I feel like I'm in an alternate universe.
Can you imagine?
Diego used to be the fat, clumsy, crybaby
bastard of this family.
Look at him now!
He's actually running for governor!
Mark my words.
If that bastard ever wins,
I'll have my head chopped off.
Raul, did I say something funny?!
No, Papa.
I was just thinking of an old saying
that if someone feels
threatened or nervous,
they usually mask it by laughter
or letting out their anger.
Just like what you're doing.
What if I shove this cane
down your throat?!
Papa, please!
Don't vent your anger on Raul.
Actually, he's right.
We should be wary of Diego
because he could win
the votes of the masses.
Papa, had you let me run in the elections.
A woman politician…
-like me.
-[Julio] Here we go again.
You know, I can get the votes of the poor.
Cut it out, Mom. You can't win. Accept it.
And we'll keep losing if we
let you run in the elections.
Wow, Arnaldo! Are you sure you'll win?
-Well, yes, I am!
-Oh.
Just stop it!
Look at you. This is so stupid!
We are punishing each other
because of what happened earlier!
When in fact it's them
who deserve our punishment!
To remind those peasants
just who they're dealing with!
[Loring] The Ardientes are the worst!
They thought they could intimidate us.
And bribe us.
No matter what they give us,
I'll never vote for any Ardiente again!
-[Pandoy] That's right!
-[Fernan] Yeah!
And they have the nerve to tell us that
Diego helped their prisoner escape.
Are those bastards crazy?
Doesn't matter.
Everyone in the cooperative should unite.
I'm for Diego!
-We're all for Diego!
-For Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
-Diego!
Thank you, Uncle. Thank you, everyone.
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello, Congressman.
Mario, are you still there?
Yes, sir. What is it, sir?
Do you need our help?
Yes.
I want you to teach
Diego Torillo a lesson.
I want you to beat some sense into him.
Yes, Congressman.
Let's go.
-[Fernan] Like his grandfather.
-[Pandoy] Right.
[Pandoy] Remember how mad
he got when we ignored it?
[Fernan] I know.
-All right. Here. Here. Here.
-You're so silly.
Everyone, look.
Diego Torillo. Come with us.
Wait. Who are you? What do you want?
Congressman Ardiente told us
to pick him up.
They have something to discuss.
[Fernan] Hold on a second.
I don't believe you. Get out of here.
I said--
-[Camia] Let go of him!
-[farmers clamoring]
Go on! Try it!
-Give us your guns!
-I dare you!
-Take their guns!
-Give us your guns!
[Pandoy] Take their guns!
-Leave!
-Get out of here!
-Out!
-What now, huh?!
-[Camia] Out!
-Get out of here!
Don't ever come back!
-[farmer 1] Don't ever come back here!
-[farmer 2] Get out of here!
[Fernan] Tell that to your boss!
-Chickens!
-Leave!
[Fernan] Still acting tough?
Did you really think you could
get away from me
after what you did earlier?
Maybe you forgot I know where you live.
About that…
Well, I was quite busy.
But actually, Mr. Mayor,
I was just about to call you
because I'm about
to open a bottle of wine.
Let's celebrate, Mr. Mayor.
One question, one straight answer.
Are you supporting another
candidate in the elections?
Where is this coming from, Mister--
I saw you earlier. You helped Diego.
Ow.
May I just remind you, Mr. Mayor…
First, we aren't together
for you to feel jealous.
Second. This day was exhausting.
I think I deserve a warm bath.
Once you're ready to talk
in a calm manner,
I'm sure you know where to find me.
[sensual music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[tense music playing]
What are you doing there?
Mr. Mayor.
Why are you here?
Well…
I thought you invited me.
Really?
I don't remember inviting you here.
I guess you misunderstood
what I said earlier.
Let me explain it to you.
What I meant was…
go home first, and once you're
calm enough to talk to me,
come back here to my house so we can talk.
I didn't say you could
come to my bathroom.
Well…
it's a good thing
I didn't come here to talk.
[suspenseful sting]
[groans]
[sighs]
[exhales]
Ivy, I told you that the more you do that,
the more I want you.
So, please. Do it again.
Go ahead. Slap me.
-Mr. Mayor, please leave.
-No more?
-I said leave.
No, because I will keep
coming back for more.
Get out.
No more? Is that all?
Oh, yes!
-Out of my room!
-Yes! Now, it's my turn.
[Ivy groans]
Arnaldo! Arnaldo!
Arnaldo!
[Ivy groans]
[tense music playing]
[Arnaldo grunts]
[groaning]
Ah!
You want more? Was that enough?
You want more?
Tell me. Do you want more?!
That was below the belt, but I'll take it.
[Arnaldo panting]
What do you want? Huh?
What do you really want, Ivy?
Look, Arnaldo.
Arnaldo, we don't have to be like this.
I'm not easy to get,
like your other women.
I'm sorry if I did that to you.
You're just so aggressive.
What I want is…
I want to know you better first.
I want to know who you
really are, your personality,
and who you are inside.
All you have to do is just make me happy.
Then, I'm all yours.
I'll give you everything!
I'm all yours.
Make you happy?
Wait.
Ouch.
I thought I wasn't like your other women.
So…
I'm just like them?
You just want me to be a bed filler?
Arnaldo…
That's not…
-what I'm trying to say.
-No, no, no, no.
Well, if that's what you think of me…
Arnaldo, you can't fool me.
You hear that?
If you want me to be your girlfriend,
if you really want me, you'll respect me.
You won't treat me like your former women.
Please go home.
Ivy.
Ivy!
Diego is really testing my patience.
And you three worthless
bastards. You maggots.
Get out of my sight! Leave!
You're all idiots!
Papa, this proves that Diego
isn't afraid of us anymore.
And will definitely influence
people to support him.
What do you want me to do, then?
Have Diego killed? Or better…
Raul is the better choice.
Do you want to keep him as a hostage
so Diego stops going against us?
Is that what you want?
[quietly] This old bastard.
No, Papa.
All I'm saying is
we have to do something about it,
or else we'll lose supporters.
That is one thing that will never happen
because the one who will defeat
the Ardientes hasn't been born.
It can happen, Papa.
Especially if Arnaldo
continues to be careless.
You know your grandson.
Instead of pleasing the dirty masses,
all he does is flirt with Ivy Aguas.
Stop it, Emilia.
Arnaldo knows what he's doing.
He is going to bring Ivy home.
And if necessary, I'll help him do it.
Now, please. Stop discrediting your son.
Whatever you say
won't change my mind, anyway.
Arnaldo will be my successor, not you.
Now, you. You're my daughter.
And I love you very much.
But… we'll talk about you some other time.
[sighs]
-Arnaldo…
-Ivy.
Arnaldo, please! Please go home.
Look, we're hurting each other.
I don't want this.
And I don't understand
what has gotten into you.
Please, just go home.
Fine. I'll admit, I was out of line.
I don't want us to fight, either.
It's just that today, I feel
like you're toying with me.
-No.
-Yes!
-How?
-With… with Diego.
I don't like it!
-You're mine, Ivy.
-[sighs]
-That Diego…
-You're all mine.
Diego… You mean that guy?
Come on, Arnaldo! Can't you see?
I'm just using Diego…
to know what his plans
are against you and your family.
You're too possessive, Mr. Mayor.
Arnaldo is the jealous type.
And I don't like that.
I hate those kinds of men.
Arnaldo…
I'm yours.
I mean, my loyalty is all yours.
Believe me, I'm loyal to you.
Come here.
[upbeat music playing]
You know, just focus on me.
In the end, you'll get what you want.
Arnaldo. Arnaldo…
You are playing a dangerous game.
[line ringing]
Hello. Ready the car.
We're going somewhere.
[ominous music playing]
[Carlotta clears throat]
Nanny.
Ivy.
Arnaldo here decided to pay a visit.
Nanny Carlotta must be
feeling uncomfortable.
Um…
Nanny, can you please escort
Arnaldo to the living room?
I just need to get dressed.
[Carlotta] Okay, Ivy.
Well, can I at least have a drink first?
Oh, sure. I'll just get dressed.
I'll be right with you.
Nanny, please keep him company.
Mr. Mayor.
Disgusting.
I feel like you're toying with me.
-How?
-With… with Diego!
That guy? Can't you see?
I'm just using Diego to know
what his plans are
against you and your family.
Ivy, I want you to trust me.
Let me protect you
because there's nothing
I wouldn't do for you.
-I need to save Jepoy!
-I'll save him.
I'm his friend, so I'll be
the one to save Jepoy.
Yes, he's your friend, but I love you!
If you get caught, you're done for.
I'll die first before that happens.
[phone ringing]
-Hello, Ivy?
-Diego?
Is there a problem? Why'd you call?
It's about what happened earlier.
I just want to ask how you're doing.
How are the people from the cooperative?
How are you? Are you okay?
Of course. I'm tough as nails.
I'm all right.
Uh, Diego, I was just thinking…
now that the Ardientes know about
your candidacy as governor…
I'm sure that they'll go after you.
Diego, it's more dangerous now.
I was thinking of giving you bodyguards.
Ivy, after everything we've been through…
you still think I need bodyguards?
I know you're worried.
Ivy, I have my own bodyguards.
The people from the cooperative.
No one can protect me
better than they can.
All of them. The people.
They're my bodyguards.
Diego, please be careful.
I promise. Take care of yourself too.
[tender music playing]
The people are willing to give
up their lives for me, Ivy.
But who will sacrifice their life for you?
Hey. Where are you going?
I'm going to Ivy's.
I'll stand guard outside her house.
Like a security guard?
If that's what it takes
to make sure she's safe.
If that's the case,
you should bring some coffee.
Come on, Loring. He doesn't need that.
As long as it's Ivy,
he's always wide awake.
Uncle, come on. Are you still
cracking that joke?
Well, you're the one who hasn't changed.
-Well, Nanny?
-Just take care out there.
[Pandoy] Yes, stay safe.
-I'll take care.
-[Loring] Okay.
Do you have a problem?
Mr. Mayor, I don't like
the fact that you harassed Ivy.
You're older than her,
so please respect her.
You know, at our house,
maids like you get punished.
Forgive me, Mr. Mayor,
but this isn't your house.
Yes, I forgive you now.
But for a maid, you're a bit meddlesome.
And for a politician,
you're quite perverted.
Again, I don't care what you think.
But be careful.
That might get you into trouble.
And that might be the reason
why you'll lose in the upcoming elections.
[doorbell rings]
Good evening.
Congressman.
Where's Miss Aguas?
Mr. Mayor.
You forgot your eyeglasses.
Thank you.
She's inside, Congressman.
Well then, I think I should come in.
I should--
Ivy, dear. The congressman's here.
Congressman.
-Grandpa.
-May I join you?
[tense music playing]
I plan to conduct a survey.
The public is losing
their trust in the Ardientes.
I can't lose to Diego.
I won't let that happen!
You know what? You are a two-faced bitch!
Diego, just like before.
Nothing will change.
Lily will always be there for you.
[Arnaldo] Well? Should I
get rid of Diego now?
Can you really kill your own brother?
[theme music playing]